Kar do
[Music]
Hello friends welcome to 519 number
printer watch last second point day
and e capsule
Shetty 6
reporters in New
Delhi today on
[Prasha]
220 of this
gallery open what is the use for mobile
phones hey I have bought a new one, it's going great well there was
no cut anywhere on the way
then I
found Rajesh Kumar Singh
that I have to pay the bill on
all the amount here also while doing which phone is it that should
always be there at that time and I swear by keeping my hand on the
last 500 grams, today news nation
today from internet user mobile phone bill
reading and writing and forest Merta road
to for infants gas to medium mother for
less ok and let's go for gold from a
that hot major column is very hot so
doctor se appointment
kar do kar do
[Music]
Ajay has